* *
**
You dance divinely.
你的舞蹈很神圣。
* *
**
- Oh, I love this song!
- 哦，我喜欢这首歌！
- Why are you nitwits
in my house?
-你们为什么是白痴
在我家吗？
We're bored!
我们很无聊！
- And we don't
want to be bored!
- 而我们不
想无聊！
- We wanna have fun.
- 我们想玩得开心。
- Come on, Squidward.
Give us something fun to do.
- 来吧，章鱼哥。
给我们一些有趣的事情做。
Please?
请？
- Oh, let's play lunch!
- 哦，我们去吃午饭吧！
- No problem.
I'll whip up some grub.
- 没问题。
我去弄点蛴螬。
- Leave my kitchen alone!
- 别碰我的厨房！
- Hm, there must be something
- 嗯，一定有什么事情
I can scavenge up around here.
我可以在这附近捡拾东西。
- Oh.
That's it.
- 哦。
就是这样。
How would you two like to
go on a... scavenger hunt?
你们两个愿意怎样
进行...寻宝游戏？
Scavenger hunt?
寻宝游戏？
- "A party game in which
the participants work in teams
- “一款派对游戏，其中
参与者以团队形式工作
to collect a list
of miscellaneous objects"!
收集清单
各种物品”！
Scavenger hunt, yeah!
寻宝游戏，耶！
What's first on the list,
Squidward?
清单上第一个是什么，
章鱼哥？
- Um, oh, uh, well,
let's see.
- 嗯，哦，呃，好吧，
让我们看看。
Bring back the rare
Desert Sandwich.
带回稀有的
沙漠三明治。
Sandwich?
三明治？
- Not in here!
- 不在这里！
The sandwich is only found
三明治才被发现
deep in the Bikini Badlands,
out there!
在比基尼荒地深处，
在那里！
- Oh.
- 哦。
- Phew.
I am a genius.
- 唷。
我是一个天才。
- Goodlands, half a league.
- 古德兰兹，半里格。
Badlands, 20,000 leagues.
荒地，20,000 联盟。
- So... thirsty.
- 所以...渴了。
Oh.
哦。
It's no use.
这是没有用的。
We'll never find
the rare Desert Sandwich.
我们永远找不到
罕见的沙漠三明治。
* *
**
- Squidward!
We did it!
- 章鱼哥！
我们做到了！
We brought back the first item!
我们带回了第一个物品！
Witch?
巫婆？
- Oh, good grief.
Not that kind of sand witch!
- 哦，真可惜。
不是那种沙之魔女！
The Desert Sandwich
has tomatoes and bread
沙漠三明治
有西红柿和面包
and--and--mayo.
和——和——蛋黄酱。
- No worries, I used to work
at an evil deli.
- 不用担心，我以前工作过
在一个邪恶的熟食店。
Ta da!
哒哒！
- Oh, looks pretty good.
- 哦，看起来不错。
Get it off!
把它脱下来！
- What's next on
our scavenger hunt, Squidward?
- 接下来是什么
我们的寻宝游戏，章鱼哥？
- Hmm... oh.
- 嗯...哦。
Mm-hmm.
嗯嗯。
Your next item is
the Boxing Begonia!
您的下一个项目是
拳击海棠！
It only grows in the deepest
canyon of the Mariana Trench.
它只生长在最深处
马里亚纳海沟的峡谷。
both: Ooh!
两人：哦！
- Ha, that'll keep them
out of my hair.
- 哈，这样就能留住他们
从我的头发里出来。
Oh.
哦。
- It's so straight-down-y.
- 太直接了。
- Don't worry, Patrick.
A scavenger is always prepared.
- 别担心，帕特里克。
拾荒者总是做好准备的。
This rope is too short!
We need another one!
这绳子太短了！
我们还需要另一个！
- Here!
- Thanks, Patrick!
- 这里！
- 谢谢，帕特里克！
Where'd you get another rope?
你从哪里得到另一根绳子？
- From that rock!
- 来自那块岩石！
- Found it!
- 找到了！
- We're back.
- 我们回来了。
But--but--it's not possible!
但是——但是——这不可能！
Boxing Begonia?
拳击海棠？
It's beautiful.
很美丽。
- The champ takes
a swift uppercut to the jaw.
快速上勾拳打中下巴。
- Squidward is
against the ropes.
- 章鱼哥是
对抗绳索。
A left, a right.
一个左，一个右。
- Oh, and the champ is down!
- 哦，冠军倒下了！
- The winner!
- 获胜者！
How do you keep
finding everything?
你如何保持
找到一切？
- You have to keep your
skull... numb.
- 你必须保留你的
头骨……麻木了。
- Yeah, we're numbskulls!
- 是啊，我们都是傻瓜！
Your next mission is to find
你的下一个任务是找到
the Loch Ness Monster
and bring him back...
尼斯湖水怪
并把他带回来...
alive.
活。
- Ooh, the Loch Ness Monster!
- 哦，尼斯湖水怪！
- Oh, so good!
Oh, so good!
- 噢，太好了！
哦，太好了！
What color?
什么颜色？
- Doesn't matter!
- 没关系！
Good luck!
祝你好运！
They'll never find it.
他们永远找不到它。
And if they do,
it'll eat them.
如果他们这样做了，
它会吃掉它们。
It's a win-win.
这是双赢的。
- Stroke! Stroke! Stroke!
- 中风！中风！中风！
Stroke! Stroke! Stroke!
中风！中风！中风！
- How are we gonna find
a monster in the dark?
- 我们怎样才能找到
黑暗中的怪物？
I can't see a thing.
我什么也看不见。
- We don't have to find it.
- 我们不必找到它。
It'll find us.
它会找到我们的。
* *
**
I'm the greatest.
我是最伟大的。
And here comes the worst.
最糟糕的情况来了。
We're back.
我们回来了。
The lo--lo--
洛——洛——
The Loch Ness Monster!
尼斯湖水怪！
How did you find it?
你是怎么找到它的？
- Oh, simple.
Bagpipes.
- 哦，简单。
风笛。
- No, it hates it.
- 不，它讨厌它。
Ah.
啊。
- But it sure loves to eat 'em.
- 但它确实喜欢吃它们。
- One very long
- 一根很长
digestive tract later...
消化道稍后...
Give us another one!
再给我们一份吧！
- Oh, brother.
- 哦，兄弟。
Give us another one!
再给我们一份吧！
- Brother...
- 兄弟...
- Come on, just one more.
- 来吧，再来一张。
- Well, all right, it's--
it's impossible, but...
- 嗯，好吧，这是--
这是不可能的，但是...
if only you could
find my long lost brother.
如果你能的话
找到我失散多年的兄弟。
Brother?
兄弟？
I haven't seen him
since he was a baby.
我没见过他
从他还是个婴儿的时候起。
- Aww.
- 哇。
- Baby with a moustache.
- 留着小胡子的婴儿。
- He was an early bloomer.
- 他是一个早熟的人。
Um...
嗯...
Aw, what a pretty name.
噢，多么漂亮的名字啊。
- If I could just
see him again...
- 如果我可以的话
再次见到他...
No.
不。
- That's so sad!
- 太悲伤了！
- Even my armpits are crying!
- 连腋窝都在流泪！
- Come on, Patrick, we've got
some extreme scavenging to do.
- 来吧，帕特里克，我们有
一些极端的清理工作要做。
- Yeah!
- 是的！
- Oh, thank you.
- 噢，谢谢。
I'm free!
我自由了！
- Squidward's brother!
- 章鱼哥的弟弟！
Squidward's brother!
章鱼哥的弟弟！
Squidward's brother?
章鱼哥的弟弟？
* *
**
- He's right here!
- 他就在这里！
Squidward's brother!
章鱼哥的弟弟！
- Rascal shaved his moustache!
- 流氓剃了胡子！
Good grief.
好悲伤。
- Six months later...
- 六个月后...
Um! Squidward's brother!
嗯！章鱼哥的弟弟！
Squidward's brother!
章鱼哥的弟弟！
Mrs. Tentacles,
you're Squidward's mother.
触手夫人，
你是章鱼哥的母亲。
You must know where
Squidward's brother is.
你一定知道在哪里
是章鱼哥的弟弟。
Squidward never had a brother.
章鱼哥从来没有兄弟。
One of him was enough.
有他一个就够了。
- Aw, that's so sad.
- 噢，太悲伤了。
Squidward wanted a baby brother
so badly he imagined one.
章鱼哥想要一个弟弟
他的想象太糟糕了。
- Oh, man. Now it'll take
even longer to find him.
- 哦，伙计。现在需要
甚至需要更长的时间才能找到他。
Oh, I'm getting a brainstorm!
哦，我正在头脑风暴！
- I've got you, buddy.
- 我找到你了，伙计。
- No, Patrick, let it flow.
- 不，帕特里克，让它顺其自然。
Ooh, I have a plan.
哦，我有一个计划。
* *
**
Meow.
喵。
* *
**
Oh, I love my two new homes.
哦，我喜欢我的两个新家。
And best of all, I haven't
最重要的是，我还没有
heard from those idiots
in months.
听那些白痴说
几个月后。
- Squidward.
- 章鱼哥。
We found your brother.
我们找到了你的兄弟。
You urchin brains!
你们这群顽童脑子！
I never had a brother!
我从来没有过兄弟！
- You do now!
- 你现在就做！
- Two brothers!
Us!
- 两个兄弟！
我们！
- What are you morons
talking about?
- 你们是什么白痴
谈论什么？
- Come on in, Mama.
- 进来吧，妈妈。
Ma
马
I've adopted
your two little friends.
我已经采用了
你的两个小朋友。
Brothers.
兄弟。
- Oh, what a beautiful family--
yeee.
- 噢，多么美好的一家人啊——
是啊。
Smile!
微笑！
* *
**